Tonight's selection:
Brussels sprouts.
(Howard:)Really?
(Howard:)You're changing the
Sheldonian calendar?
(Sheldon:)It's a small price to pay.
For what?
(Leonard:)No, no, don't ask.
Sorry, sorry, sorry,
sorry, sorry.
(Sheldon:)In order to live long enough
to fuse my consciousness
(Sheldon:)with cybernetics,
I need to change my diet.
(Penny:)Wait. Cybernetics is
robot stuff, right?
(Sheldon:)Correct.
(Penny:)So you want to turn yourself
(Penny:)into some sort of robot?
(Sheldon:)Essentially, yes.
(Penny:)Okay, here's my question.
(Penny:)Didn't you already do that?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Flattering, but sadly, no.
(Sheldon:)I'm also planning
to begin an exercise regimen
(Sheldon:)designed to strengthen
my cardiovascular system.
(Sheldon:)AKA jogging.
(Penny:)Wait. Honey,
have you ever run before?
(Sheldon:)Certainly.
(Sheldon:)I've run from bullies, dogs,
angry chickens...
(Sheldon:)and one particularly
persistent P.E. teacher
(Sheldon:)determined to bend me over
and give me a scoliosis test.